BRITTANY HUBER

PRODUCT SUPPORT SPECIALIST

▶ brittanyleighhuber@gmail.com **♦** bhuber23.github.io **♦** 3039607370 **♦** Aurora, CO **in** brittany-huber-6217ba139/ **♦** bhuber23

SUMMARY

Motivated support specialist with over 5 years experience in customer service and support. Transitioned to technical support roles which involve troubleshooting and being able to resolve issues timely and effectively. Currently enrolled in the University of Denver Full Stack Coding Bootcamp to learn web development skills and expand my technical knowledge. Looking forward to new opportunities within the development field after mastering the necessary skills.

EMPLOYMENT

Mar. 2019 to Current RE/MAX, LLC · Product Support Specialist · Denver, CO

As a Product Support Specialist, I support the RE/MAX membership with any technical issues experienced with the products provided to RE/MAX affiliates. I troubleshoot the various issues experienced and when needed will escalate tickets for any bugs found to our internal development teams or third party vendors. Using Salesforce, I manage incoming tickets via email and live chat, while also taking live phone calls to help resolve issues over the phone.

Apr. 2017 to Mar. 2019

Zillow Group · Client Engagement Specialist · Denver, CO In my role as a Client Engagement Specialist I would connect consumers with real estate agents who had inquired about homes on the Zillow Group websites. Because of my expertise and overall success, I was also a member of the SOP Advisory Board in which I would help draft and develop standard operating procedures for our department to adhere to. The role involved some troubleshooting aspects in which I would assist both agents and consumers with issues they'd experience and when necessary escalate the issues to the appropriate departments.

Sept. 2013 to Nov. 2016

Sunglass Hut · Sales Manager · Lone Tree, CO

As a Sales Manager, I helped ensure that all sales goals for the store were met or exceeded. I managed other staff members to help meet their goals while exceeding my personal goals for one of the top performing stores in the region. In addition to this, I maintained store paperwork to comply with company audits and ensured operational excellence.

EDUCATION

Sept. 2019 to Current

University of Denver - Full Stack Bootcamp

Aug. 2007 to May 2010 University of Colorado - Boulder

SKILLS

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Salesforce, Zendesk, Windows, Microsoft Office